### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to auto.ratesforinsurance.com. This privacy policy describes how auto.ratesforinsurance.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: auto.ratesforinsurance.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information.

#### Information Collection and Use

auto.ratesforinsurance.com collects information on auto.ratesforinsurance.com at several different points on our Web site. If you request an insurance quote, we require that you provide certain personally identifiable information, including your name, address email address, and phone number. This information is necessary to process your request and to contact you if necessary. Once you have entered your name, address and email address your information is then passed onto a third party company in order to supply you with information that best fits your needs.

#### Accessing Your Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at info@ratesforinsurancecom or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Agents/Service Providers

We may provide your personally identifiable information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We share aggregated information with our partners to fulfill information requests in certain states which users shared information.

We may share your information with affiliates and redirect users to third-party Web sites. auto.ratesforinsurance.com does not control the content of or the information collected from these third-party Web sites. These third-party Web sites are not subject to auto.ratesforinsurance.com's Privacy Policy. Redirects to third-party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by auto.ratesforinsurance.com of the content, policies, or practices of such sites. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these sites before you disclose your personally identifiable information to these other parties. We do not share Personally identifiable information with third parties other than as described in this privacy statement.

#### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

#### Log Files and Cookies

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

#### Cookies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by auto.ratesforinsurance.com and our partners, marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

#### Behavioral Targeting/ Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.

#### Security

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive personally identifiable information on our application form, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and follow generally accepted industry standards to protect information submitted to us, both during the transmission and once received. No method of transmission over the Internet, or electronic storage is 100 % secure and although we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Business Transitions

In the event auto.ratesforinsurance.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

#### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button \[and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site\]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Links to Other Sites

If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave auto.ratesforinsurance.com and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as auto.ratesforinsurance.com. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to auto.ratesforinsurance.com, you should read that site's privacy statement before providing any personally identifiable information.

When you subscribe to our articles by email we use a third party email service provider whose privacy statement governs the collection and use of the personally identifiable information that you have entered.

#### Changes to this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of posting a prominent notice on our homepage prior to the change becoming effective.

© Copyright 2024. Rates For Insurance. All Rights Reserved.
